You have a really cool project ahead of you.
我们准备了一个非常酷的实战项目
Our partners at Figure Eight are providing
合作伙伴 Figure Eight 提供了
pre-labeled tweets and text messages from real life disasters.
带标签的推特和短信 这些都是真实灾害里的真实数据
Your task is to repair this data with an ETL pipeline
你的任务是用ETL管道整理好这些数据
and then use a machine learning pipeline to build a supervised learning model.
然后用机器学习管道构建监督学习模型
Before you start, Robert is going to give us some background on where
在开始之前 Robert 会向我们介绍数据的来源
the data set came from and how Figure Eight prepare the data for us.
以及 Figure Eight 为我们准备的数据
Thank you. So, this is one of one most important problems that
谢谢这是我们目前试图用数据科学和机器学习解决的
we're trying to solve in data science and machine learning right now.
一个非常重要的问题
Following a disaster, typically you will get
一场灾害过后 通常人们会
millions and millions of communications either direct or via social media,
给其他人或者在社交媒体上发出大量的消息
right at the time when disaster response organizations have
而这个时候恰恰是灾害援救组织
the least capacity to filter and then pull out the messages which are the most important.
最难以从海量消息中提取那些重要消息的时候
Often it really is only one in every thousand messages that
通常几千条信息中只有一条
might be relevant to the exact response professionals.
包含应对专家想要知道的信息
So, the way that disasters are typically responded to
通常 应对灾害的方法
is that different organizations will take care of different parts of the problem.
是不同的组织部门关注不同的问题
So, one organization one care about water,
比如 一个组织关注供水
another will care about blocked roads another will care about medical supplies.
一个关注道路阻塞 一个关注医疗保障
So, when you look at the data,
所以 你在观察数据的时候
you'll see that these are
就会发现
the categories that we have pulled out for each of these data sets.
从这些数据集取得的数据都标注了对应的问题类型
So, we actually used Figure Eight from many
我们用 Figure Eight 分析
of the disasters from which these messages are taken.
各种灾害时人们发出的消息
We've then combined these data sets and relabeled them,
我们将这些信息组合起来并重新标注
so that there are consistent labels across their different disasters.
不同灾害中会有一些一样的标签
This is to allow you to investigate the different trends that you
这也可以让你得以探索并发现一些不同的趋势
might be able to find and to build supervised machine learning models.
和搭建机器学习模型
So, you'll see for example,
我们来看一个例子
when you look at a keyword like water that's actually
你看到这个关键词 水
a very small percent of the time that that will
就表明有可能对应着
map to someone who needs fresh drinking water.
一个需要干净的饮用水的人
Also that we'll miss people who say they're thirsty but don't use the word water.
同时我们也可能会漏掉那些需要饮用水 但没有提到 水 这个字的人
So, supervised machine learning based approaches are going
所以 基于监督机器学习的方法
to be a lot more accurate than anyone could do with keyword searching.
将比基于关键词搜索的方法得到更准确的结果
But this is actually a big gap right now in disaster response contexts.
目前这两者在灾害应对场景下仍有巨大的差别
So I, really look forward to seeing what you
我很期待看到下个项目中
build in your projects and hopefully discover
你搭建的模型
new trends and new ways of building
希望你能发现一些新的趋势
machine learning models that can help us respond to future disasters.
和一些构建机器学习模型的新方法来应对将要发生的灾害
One of my favorite parts about this project is how meaningful the work is.
这个项目中我最喜欢的一部分是这项工作的意义
Think about the benefits this solution brings to
想想这项成果能够造福全世界
people affected by natural disasters around the world.
帮助那些受苦于自然灾害影响的人们
Good luck with your projects and I look forward to seeing the results.
祝你好运 期待看到你的成果